{
  "sections": [
    {
      "title": "File",
      "chats": [
        {
          "indexTitle": "Format",
          "question": "Format",
          "answer": "1. Section is month.year  \n2. Index Title and Question is day  \n3. Answer is numbered list with description below point, marked with *  ",
          "dateTime": "2024-02-16T14:25:36.694Z"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "title": "02.2024",
      "chats": [
        {
          "indexTitle": "08",
          "question": "08",
          "answer": "1. [MUSK FANS: Thunderf00t is a GRIFTER FOR THE CLICKS!!!](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5T8auUw2RnQ) \n    * Scientists, debunking potential frauds, talks about this, his job, and life",
          "dateTime": "2024-02-16T14:27:34.608Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "11",
          "question": "11",
          "answer": "1. [KRÓLOWIE ŻYTA Sezon 5 odc. 1 I Kabaret Malina I ZAKUP ZETORA](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wLkpSnFbSwc)  \n    * Comedy show made by real polish farmers\n2. [A Job Is A Job | The Tim Dillon Show #381](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=I1pQv0WdIyo)  \n    * Strong comedy show commenting over news  \n3. [Louis C.K. at the Dolby](https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=OLAK5uy_mauqctx3ksO-hUs51sKtgReB6EFzdSBf0)  \n    * Well oiled cute jokes that work",
          "dateTime": "2024-02-16T14:32:15.672Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "12",
          "question": "12",
          "answer": "1. [Mingles with Jingles Episode 515 - Games of 2024 Roundup](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OwgFpUMyKsQ)  \n    * Games in production jingles waits for  \n2. [Hilarious](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RelLczY9EWk&list=OLAK5uy_mF-SqQ_TabVAu2G667LlDPNj5mg5r6hy0)  \n    * Stong jokes  ",
          "dateTime": "2024-02-16T14:36:09.473Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "13",
          "question": "13",
          "answer": "1. [Desert Of Love | Ancient Mesopotamia](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TuiVatgQEII)  \n    * Calm music\n",
          "dateTime": "2024-02-16T14:37:28.716Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "15",
          "question": "15",
          "answer": "1. [Sieci komputerowe E13 E15 E16 EE08](https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLOYHgt8dIdoz2fyn0gv4fs2t4tayalsh3)  \n    * video 1 watched in background, not attentive; todo: continue",
          "dateTime": "2024-02-16T14:41:18.261Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "16",
          "question": "16",
          "answer": "* Stories of old man from chanell Rusty78609  \n1. [MY FIRST VIDEO...9/20/2011...repost](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ivtJhJHMcfA)  \n2. [Texas...old man...me...rusty's place...](https://youtu.be/Jlk6j0kdE7w?feature=shared)  \n3. [Texas...old man...me...BEER THIRTY!!!](https://youtu.be/evhDf8_CCe0?feature=shared)  \n4. [Texas...old man...me...rusty's place...](https://youtu.be/LgrxooPcDW0?feature=shared)  \n5. [Texas...Rusty...morning video...](https://youtu.be/G14tFqcvKY4?feature=shared)  \n6. [Texas...Rusty...good morning...](https://youtu.be/83tQKogehbg?feature=shared)  \n7. [October 16, 2015](https://youtu.be/98WD4MWNSxc?feature=shared)  \n8. [Me...doing nothing...](https://youtu.be/tNr9cbUMw2U?feature=shared)  \n9. [Beerthirty...in Texas Usa...](https://youtu.be/TvkjdFQx5-Y?feature=shared)  \n10. [1st cruising video...Sausage trip](https://youtu.be/RWxdZ11G61I?feature=shared)  \n11. [Back roads of Texas...and old Texas bar info at the end...](https://youtu.be/VKcb5k6f6CY?feature=shared)\n12. [Slab, Kingsland, Texas 10/22/15. rusty78609](https://youtu.be/Rgg7bFEffCY?feature=shared)  \n13. [Sausage at Miller's 10/23/15](https://youtu.be/lyKGN6wnMDY?feature=shared)  \n14. [Whorehouse Texas 10/23/15](https://youtu.be/c4SfCmCv7rQ?feature=shared)  \n15. [Going to get sausage 10/23/15](https://youtu.be/B_Kr9MW5jjg?feature=shared)  \n16. [Jean...potholders...10/24/15](https://youtu.be/vYWJGrUDye4?feature=shared)  \n17. [FM Antenna 10/27/15](https://youtu.be/UzBDwYQltbk?feature=shared)  \n18. [Texas thinking...](https://youtu.be/hPlYcNoindM?feature=shared)  \n19. [Camping in a Prius...](https://youtu.be/B1oQjz1fktQ?feature=shared)  \n20. [Bluffton cemetery 10/23/15](https://youtu.be/INsRuQpbhCs?feature=shared)  \n21. [Prius camping part 2](https://youtu.be/29p627ezuHg?feature=shared)  \n22. [Camping in a Prius](https://youtu.be/-ikcBCoWyCk?feature=shared)    \n23. [Camping in a Prius](https://youtu.be/IOo4fTPEGzc?feature=shared)   \n24. [Camping in a Prius? Here's how to do it...](https://youtu.be/42KzDyrjr_A?feature=shared)   \n25. [Prius camping...window visors](https://youtu.be/OsPdN0RKczQ?feature=shared)   \n26. [Camping in a Prius window visors...I'll get better at this...](https://youtu.be/iP47U3vVVL0?feature=shared)   \n27. [Camping in a Prius...Cheap, comfortable camping!!!](https://youtu.be/YDI4UeBjZ5Y?feature=shared)   \n28. [Camping tips](https://youtu.be/5EN7nbKGGCM?feature=shared)   \n29. [Buying a Used/Preowned RV...this will help you...](https://youtu.be/IavknufKDAU?feature=shared)   \n30. [HOW TO MAKE CHEAP COTTON PILLOWS!!!](https://youtu.be/NpVr14ht1Cw?feature=shared)   ",
          "dateTime": "2024-02-16T14:58:50.649Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "19",
          "question": "19",
          "answer": "1. The Lord of the Rings Fellowship part 1\n    * classic from file",
          "dateTime": "2024-02-19T12:23:30.045Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "23",
          "question": "23",
          "answer": "1. [World of Warships - Cat and Mouse](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rzXnx6f823I)  \n    *\n2. [KRÓLOWIE ŻYTA Sezon 5 odc. 2 I Kabaret Malina I ZAPOWIEDŹ](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oc4qVnzwcZg)  \n    *\n3. [From 68 Cents to $18: The Inflation Shockwave at McDonald's | Mike Maloney & Alan Hibbard](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OwjSmbY2bdg)  \n    *",
          "dateTime": "2024-02-23T14:39:34.467Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "24",
          "question": "24",
          "answer": "* in backgroud doing something  \n[Price Of Poison | The Tim Dillon Show #379](https://youtu.be/x5JBng8KRYo)  \n[Prigozhin Eras Tour | The Tim Dillon Show #358](https://youtu.be/LdelkZk3YM8) 20 min  \n\n[Leave It Online | The Tim Dillon Show #382](https://youtu.be/_ea8bwU45hU)\nTwo Towers Part1 (audiobook)  \n\n[Robocop Rogue City - The Future of Law Enforcement](https://youtu.be/X5T2YaQUj-Q)  \n[KRÓLOWIE ŻYTA Sezon 5 odc. 2 I Kabaret Malina](https://www.youtube.com/kabaretmalina/videos)",
          "dateTime": "2024-02-24T16:16:17.147Z"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}